# Siddharth Bhardwaj

2280 Baronwood drive, Oakville L6M5J8 \* Mobile 905-483-0996 Email : siddharthbhardwaj96@yahoo.com

# **Customer Service Representative**

Providing Exceptional Service...Building Loyal Relationships...Solving Problems...Increasing Sales

- Dynamic customer service professional experienced in retail store settings
- Excel in listening to customer needs, articulating product benefits and providing solutions that add value to the customer
- Build and maintain enduring customer relationships to boost sales and generate repeat business

## Summary

Student studying Software Engineering with experience and extensive education in software design, object oriented programming and application development. A fast learner with an ability to understand new concepts quickly and apply them at high level. Strong work ethic in team or individual settings to drive product success and process of efficiency. Strong time management, troubleshooting and problem solving skills with an analytical mindset.

### **Technical Profile:**

Languages: C, Java, Unix, RISC-V Assembly, MATLAB, Verilog HDL, HTML, Turing

Platforms and Frameworks: Windows, Mac OSX, Linux

**Software**: Git Bash, Microsoft Office, Eclipse, Visual Studio, Adobe Photoshop, Google

Drive, Dropbox

Hardware: Arduino board, Oscilloscopes, function generators, digital multimeters,

moving various robots using Java

### **Education:**

Software Engineering (Honor) – York University Expected Graduation: Spring 2020

• Coursework: Software Development and Design, Systems Programming, Software Engineering Analysis, Software Modeling, and Computer Program Design

White Oaks Secondary School – Oakville

# Siddharth Bhardwaj

2280 Baronwood drive, Oakville L6M5J8 \* Mobile 905-483-0996 Email : siddharthbhardwaj96@yahoo.com

• International Baccalaureate(IB) program

## **Relevant Projects:**

Barille Simulator: <a href="https://github.com/SidB16">https://github.com/SidB16</a>

- Developed software for a hardware device used to help kids read Braille. For a class project where the hardware device had a number of Braille cells, as well as a number of physical buttons. The system would present Braille characters/words to the user who would then respond by pressing buttons
- Used Git for version control. Utilized features such as pull and push local updates to a repository
- Utilized J-Unit testing to debug and develop test cases for testing program
- Improved program runtime by developing efficient algorithms that were also simple and easy to follow for other team members

## **Experience:**

### **TD Canada Trust, Burlington**

August 2014 till present

### **Customer Service Representative**

- Dynamic customer service professional experienced in retail store settings
- Excel in listening to customer needs, articulating product benefits and providing solutions that add value to the customer
- Build and maintain enduring customer relationships to boost sales and generate repeat business
- Exceeded sales targets and unit increased productivity
- Worked with multiple finance related software to perform various banking transactions.

#### **Excel Lassonde, Toronto**

September 2016 - April 2017

### **Financial Director**

- Managed and monitored financial data through cloud database system
- Performed weekly analysis of organization through software analytics to provide consultation that would maximize company profits
- Created posters and graphics for recruitment and various events
- Interviewed tutoring applicants

# Siddharth Bhardwaj

2280 Baronwood drive, Oakville L6M5J8 \* Mobile 905-483-0996 Email : siddharthbhardwaj96@yahoo.com

### **Canadian Tire, Oakville**

#### **Customer Service Representative**

#### August 2013- February 2014

- Respond to telephone inquiries, providing quality service to customers and associates inquiring about the products
- Access electronic and paper cataloging systems to look up product information and availability
- Strive for quick complaint resolutions on the first call and avoid escalation of issues
- Demonstrate effective communication with customers with diverse backgrounds
- Ensure customers were satisfied with every part of the flooring experience from initial greeting through final purchase of the product
- Memorize the company's product offerings and confidently communicate product benefits and provide excellent service

### The Hamilton Golf and Country Club

### Caddie (summer time)

July 2012- September 2012

- Carrying Golf Bags or pushes or pull that hold golf bag around golf course for players
- Advising players as requested on selection of proper club for stroke or concerning peculiarities of course
- Building rapport with customers and developing customer relationships

### **Extracurricular Activities:**

•York Marketing Association(YMA) •York Finance Club (YFS) •Lassonde Student Body Government •Industrial Insight Initiative, providing clubs at Lassonde with any assistance financial or consulting •York Student Federation(YFS) RedPack volunteer •TD Tree-Days volunteer, planting trees across ontario to help the environment.

## Languages:

•English •Hindi •Urdu •Guajarati •Punjabi •Spanish